Do you benefit more from investing?
But then the return must be greater than the interest rate you pay on the loan.
And now, given that interest rates are rising, we have to look more at your economy
-To know whether to amortize or not.
-Fast and moving?
-Fast interest means bound interest rate.
You commit to a certain interest rate for one, two or three years.
-The motion rate changes every three months.
-What do you like the most?
Variable interest rates have been cheaper for long periods.
-But you should be able to sleep well at night ... -is in your stomach ...
And you must afford interest rates as they rise.
-The interest rate queen.
-The interest rate queen ... oh.